<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipe of the Week</title>
    <link>http://www.rso.cornell.edu/foodforthought/Site/Recipe_of_the_Week</link>
    <description>Looking for international variety, tropical wonders, or simply something new? Follow our Recipe of the Week blog and discover something new! </description>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Trifle</title>
      <link>http://www.rso.cornell.edu/foodforthought/Site/Recipe_of_the_Week/Entries/2011/10/5_Challah_2.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a848548-1b26-40d8-99ea-97b40405c084</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Oct 2011 18:19:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>By: Stella Zedman&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A traditional trifle of berries, peaches and bananas, layered between slices of sponge cake, vanilla pudding and whipped cream, is sure to impress your guests and make a sensational centerpiece for your holiday sweet table.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ingredients&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	1 recipe Golden Yellow Cake (or purchased pound cake or sponge cake)&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	6 cups (1.5&#xA0;L) strawberries, raspberries, blueberries, peaches, bananas or any combination (fresh or frozen)&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	1/4 cup (50 mL) sugar&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	1 packet vanilla pudding mix, prepared&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	1/4 cup (50 mL) sherry or liqueur (any kind you like)&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	1 cup (250 mL) raspberry or apricot jam&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	2 cups (500 mL) whipping cream&lt;br/&gt;	&#x2022;	additional whole berries or fruit for decorating&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Directions&lt;br/&gt;	1.	Cut the cake into slices (uneven or ragged is fine). Prepare whatever fruit you're using and cut into 1/2-inch (1-cm) pieces, if necessary. Place in a bowl and toss fruit with the sugar. Prepare the vanilla pudding. You'll need an attractive glass bowl, about 8 inches (20 cm) in diameter. Arrange about half of the cake pieces to cover the bottom of the bowl and sprinkle with about half of the sherry or liqueur. Spread cake pieces with half of the jam, then top with half of the fruit.&lt;br/&gt;	2.	Cover the fruit with half of the vanilla pudding, followed by half of the whipped cream. Repeat the layers: the remaining cake, sherry, jam, fruit and pudding.&lt;br/&gt;	3.	Finally, cover the top completely with the remaining whipped cream. Decorate with additional whole berries or fruit pieces. Cover with plastic wrap and refrigerate for at least 6 hours or overnight before serving.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Source: &lt;a href="http://allrecipes.com/Recipe/challah-i/detail.aspx"&gt;http://recipes.kaboose.com/holiday-trifle.html&lt;/a&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/images.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://www.rso.cornell.edu/foodforthought/Site/Recipe_of_the_Week/Entries/2011/10/5_Challah_2.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challah</title>
      <link>http://www.rso.cornell.edu/foodforthought/Site/Recipe_of_the_Week/Entries/2011/9/28_Challah.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6b5f53c-c7df-4e53-be93-5d3164fd26c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>By: Joan Callaway&#xA0;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Traditional egg bread for the Jewish Sabbath. You can add 1 cup raisins or golden raisins to the dough just before shaping and then make the loafs into round braids for Rosh Hashanah.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ingredients&lt;br/&gt;		2 1/2 cups warm water (110 degrees F/45 degrees C)&lt;br/&gt;		1 tablespoon active dry yeast&lt;br/&gt;		1/2 cup honey&lt;br/&gt;		4 tablespoons vegetable oil&lt;br/&gt;		3 eggs&lt;br/&gt;		1 tablespoon salt&lt;br/&gt;		8 cups unbleached all-purpose flour&lt;br/&gt;		1 tablespoon poppy seeds (optional)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Directions&lt;br/&gt;	1.	In a large bowl, sprinkle yeast over barely warm water. Beat in honey, oil, 2 eggs, and salt. Add the flour one cup at a time, beating after each addition, graduating to kneading with hands as dough thickens. Knead until smooth and elastic and no longer sticky, adding flour as needed. Cover with a damp clean cloth and let rise for 1 1/2 hours or until dough has doubled in bulk.&lt;br/&gt;	2.	Punch down the risen dough and turn out onto floured board. Divide in half and knead each half for five minutes or so, adding flour as needed to keep from getting sticky. Divide each half into thirds and roll into long snake about 1 1/2 inches in diameter. Pinch the ends of the three snakes together firmly and braid from middle. Either leave as braid or form into a round braided loaf by bringing ends together, curving braid into a circle, pinch ends together. Grease two baking trays and place finished braid or round on each. Cover with towel and let rise about one hour.&lt;br/&gt;	3.	Preheat oven to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C).&lt;br/&gt;	4.	Beat the remaining egg and brush a generous amount over each braid. Sprinkle with poppy seeds if desired.&lt;br/&gt;	5.	Bake at 375 degrees F (190 degrees C) for about 40 minutes. Bread should have a nice hollow sound when thumped on the bottom. Cool on a rack for at least one hour before slicing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Source: &lt;a href="http://allrecipes.com/Recipe/challah-i/detail.aspx"&gt;http://allrecipes.com/Recipe/challah-i/detail.aspx&lt;/a&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/144853.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://www.rso.cornell.edu/foodforthought/Site/Recipe_of_the_Week/Entries/2011/9/28_Challah.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, MMMM d, y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://www.rso.cornell.edu/foodforthought/Site/Recipe_of_the_Week</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>5</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
